[
  {
    "answer": "command+x",
    "question": "How do you cut the selected item and copy it to the clipboard?",
    "keys": [91, 88]
  },
  {
    "answer": "command+c",
    "question": "How do you copy the selected item to the clipboard?",
    "keys": [91, 67]
  },
  {
    "answer": "command+v",
    "question": "How do you paste the contents of the clipboard into the current document or app?",
    "keys": [91, 86]
  },
  {
    "answer": "command+z",
    "question": "How do you undo the previous command?",
    "keys": [91, 90]
  },
  {
    "answer": "command+Shift+z",
    "question": "How do you redo to reverse the undo command?",
    "keys": [91, 16, 90]
  },
  {
    "answer": "command+a",
    "question": "How do you select all items?",
    "keys": [91, 65]
  },
  {
    "answer": "command+f",
    "question": "How do you find items in a document or open a Find window?",
    "keys": [91, 70]
  },
  {
    "answer": "command+g",
    "question": "How do you find the next occurrence of the item previously found?",
    "keys": [91, 71]
  },
  {
    "answer": "command+h",
    "question": "How do you hide the windows of the front (active) app?",
    "keys": [91, 72]
  },
  {
    "answer": "command+Option+h",
    "question": "How do you view the front (active) app but hide all other apps?",
    "keys": [91, 18, 72]
  },
  {
    "answer": "command+k",
    "question": "How do you clear the screen using the command key?",
    "keys": [91, 75]
  },
  {
    "answer": "command+m",
    "question": "How do you minimize the front window to the Dock?",
    "keys": [91, 77]
  },
  {
    "answer": "command+Option+m",
    "question": "How do you minimize all windows of the front app?",
    "keys": [91, 18, 77]
  },
  {
    "answer": "command+n",
    "question": "How do you open a new document or window?",
    "keys": [91, 78]
  },
  {
    "answer": "command+t",
    "question": "How do you open a new tab?",
    "keys": [91, 84]
  },
  {
    "answer": "command+o",
    "question": "How do you open the selected item, or open a dialog to select a file to open?",
    "keys": [91, 79]
  },
  {
    "answer": "command+p",
    "question": "How do you print the current document?",
    "keys": [91, 80]
  },
  {
    "answer": "command+s",
    "question": "How do you save the current document?",
    "keys": [91, 83]
  },
  {
    "answer": "Option+command+Esc",
    "question": "How do you force quit?",
    "keys": [18, 91, 27]
  },
  {
    "answer": "command+Space",
    "question": "How do you show or hide the Spotlight search field?",
    "keys": [91, 32]
  },
  {
    "answer": "command+Tab",
    "question": "How do you switch to the next most recently used app among your open apps?",
    "keys": [91, 9]
  },
  {
    "answer": "Shift+command+Tilde(~)",
    "question": "How do you switch to the next most recently used window of the front app?",
    "keys": [16 ,91, 192]
  },
  {
    "answer": "control+a",
    "question": "How do you go to the beginning of the line you are currently typing on?",
    "keys": [17, 65]
  },
  {
    "answer": "control+e",
    "question": "How do you go to the end of the line you are currently typing on?",
    "keys": [17, 69]
  },
  {
    "answer": "control+q",
    "question": "How do you clear everything on the current line?",
    "keys": [17, 81]
  },
  {
    "answer": "control+l",
    "question": "How do you clear the screen using the control key?",
    "keys": [17, 76]
  },
  {
    "answer": "control+k",
    "question": "How do you cut everything forward to the end of the line?",
    "keys": [17, 75]
  },
  {
    "answer": "control+u",
    "question": "How do you cut everything backwards to the beginning of the line?",
    "keys": [17, 85]
  },
  {
    "answer": "control+w",
    "question": "How do you cut one word backwards using white space as the delimiter?",
    "keys": [17, 87]
  },
  {
    "answer": "control+y",
    "question": "How do you paste whatever was cut by the last cut command?",
    "keys": [17, 89]
  },
  {
    "answer": "Shift+command+3",
    "question": "How do you take a screenshot of the entire screen?",
    "keys": [16 ,91, 51]
  },
  {
    "answer": "command+Comma(,)",
    "question": "How do you open preferences for the front app?",
    "keys": [91, 188]
  }
]
